deal4loans.com 2011-12-16

# Privacy Policy - Deal4loans.com's Services | Online Loan Application And Information

By registering yourself at www.deal4loans.com you are authorizing us & our associate partners to give you a call to offer you their services for the product you have opted for, imparting product knowledge, offering promotional offers running on website & offers offered by the associated third parties. And Irrespective of the fact if also you have registered yourself under DND or DNC service still you authorize us to give you a call from the deal4loans.com & associate partners for the above mentioned purposes till 45 days of your registration with us. **Also based on your active opt-in you are open to receive promotional offers from advertiser/partnering website hence there is no DNC check required thereforth**

By accepting our 

_"Terms and Conditions"_

you authorize our partners to run a Cibil/Satyam check for your profile.

Deal4loans.com doesn't provide Loans on its own but ensures your information is sent to bank which you have opted for.Deal4loans has no sales team on its own and we just help you to compare loans .All loans are on discretion of the associated Banks.

This Privacy Policy covers **Deal4loans.com's** treatment of personally identifiable information that **Deal4loans.com** collects when you are on the Deal4loans.com site, and when you use **Deal4loans.com 's** services. This policy also covers Deal4loans.com's treatment of any personally identifiable information that Deal4loans.com's business partners share with **Deal4loans.com**. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that **Deal4loans.com** does not own or control, or to people that **Deal4loans.com** does not employ or manage. 

• **Deal4loans.com** collects personally identifiable information when you register for an **Deal4loans.com** account, when you use certain **Deal4loans.com** products or services, when you visit **Deal4loans.com** pages, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. Deal4loans.com may also receive personally identifiable information from our business partners.   
When you register with **Deal4loans.com** , we ask for your first name, last name, time zone, zip/postal code, country, state, city, email, birth date, and gender. Once you register with **Deal4loans.com** and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.   
Also during registration, you will be requested to register your mobile phone and email id, pager, or other device to receive text messages, notifications, and other services to your wireless device. By registration you authorize us to send sms/email alerts to you for your login details and alerts on bidders requests or some advertising messages/emails from us.   
If at any time you wish to stop these sms/email alerts all you have to do is write an email to us customercare@deal4loans.com with your mobile numbers and your mobile number will be deleted from the alerts list.

• **Information Sharing and Disclosure**  
**Deal4loans.com** will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone other than as specifically noted herein. Notwithstanding the foregoing, **Deal4loans.com** may sell and/or transfer your personally identifiable information to an affiliate and to any successor-in-interest as a result of a sale of any part of **Deal4loans.com's** business or upon the merger, reorganization or consolidation of **Deal4loans.com** with another entity on a basis that Deal4loans.com is not the surviving entity. For the purposes of this paragraph, "affiliate" means any person directly, or indirectly through one or more intermediaries, that controls, is controlled by or is under common control with **Deal4loans.com**. The term "control," as used in the immediately preceding sentence, shall mean with respect to any person, the possession, directly or indirectly, of the power, through the exercise of voting rights, contractual rights or otherwise, to direct or cause the direction of the management or policies of the controlled person. As used in this Privacy Policy, the term "person" includes any natural person, corporation, partnership, limited liability company, trust, unincorporated association or any other entity. 

• **Third Party Advertising**   
We may use third-party advertising companies and/or ad agencies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

• **Privacy Policy Changes**   
**Deal4loans.com** may amend this policy from time to time, at our discretion. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting the changes here on these Privacy Policy pages.
